<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">TourGuide</string>

    <string name="desc">At the point where Brazil
                Paraguay, and Argentina meet, the Iguaçu river drops spectacularly in a semicircle of 247 waterfalls that thunder down into the gorge below.
                Just above the falls, the river is constricted to one-fourth of its usual width, making the force of the water even stronger.
                 Some of the falls are more than 100 meters high and they cover such a broad area that you ll never see all of them at once,
                but you do get the broadest panorama from the Brazilian side. Catwalks and a tower give you different perspectives,
                and one bridge reaches all the way to one of the largest,
                 known as the Garganta do Diabo (Devils Throat).
                You can cross to the Argentinian side for closer views from catwalks that extend farther into the center of the falls.
                The two sides offer different perspectives and views,
                 so most tourists plan to see both. The falls are protected by the UNESCO-acclaimed Iguaçu National Park,
                 where subtropical rain forests are the home to more than 1,000 species of birds and mammals, including deer, otters, ocelots, and capybaras</string>


    <string name="desc2">"With arms outstretched 28 meters, as if to encompass all of humanity,the colossal Art Deco statue of Christ, called Cristo Redentor (Christ the Redeemer),gazes out over Rio de Janeiro and the bay from the summit of Corcovado.The 709-meter height on which it stands is part of the Tijuca National Park,and a rack railway climbs 3.5 kilometers to its top, where a broad plaza surrounds the statue. Completed in 1931the 30-meter statue was the work of Polish-French sculptor Paul Landowski and Brazilian engineer Heitor da Silva Costa,and is constructed of reinforced concrete and soapstone. The eight-meter base encloses a chapel that is popular for weddings.Although this is one of Brazil's most readily recognized icons, it is often mistakenly called The Christ of the Andes,confused with the older statue marking the boundary between Argentina and Chile.</string>






</resources>